If O-Ren was number one,
Unless she's being tricky.
Vernita Green will be number two.
Los Angeles
Vernita's in Pasadena.
But the woman you want will hole up in a low budget motel,
15 or 20 minutes away from stepping on board
a plane departing LAX
If I had to bet...
I'd say Hawthorne.
California,
Here I come.
I can't reach it.
Come on, lady - hey!
THE BRIDE: Two down,
three to go.
That's my ice cream.
You're so mean.
Konnichiwa!
Konnichiwa?
Yuki?
Bingo!
One way.
Sure.
Yuki.
You bet.
Okay.
You think you are safe?
Well, I say. Ha!
Stay in your house and get down on the floor!
Gotcha!
You fucking bitch!
You shot me in my breast!
You fucking asshole!
Now I'm always gonna have a dimple.
Piss me off!
Yuki!
In about two minutes,
It's gonna be an army of police here.
So if you're going to kill me,
now's the time.
So what's it going to be, bitch?
Goddamn.
What a wildcat!